altrooz.com 2019-06-22

# Altrooz | Privacy Policy

### Privacy Policy

### Please review our privacy policy so we can bring you the best advertising experience possible

Altrooz is committed to protecting consumer privacy and to clearly informing users about the collection and use of information when using our services. As a result, we have put together this Privacy Policy to explain how we collect and use certain information. This Privacy Policy and the opt-out choices below apply to Altrooz's mobile advertising products and services (collectively, our “Service”). This Privacy Policy also applies to our company websites located at www.altrooz.com, (collectively, our “Website”). 

##### Our Business

Altrooz is a mobile advertising company. We use our proprietary technology to offer advertising solutions to our clients, which includes working with advertisers to deliver their advertising campaigns across our network of mobile publishers and application (“app”) developers (our “Platform”). 

##### Information Collection and Sharing

Website Data Collection. Altrooz is the sole owner of the information collected on our Websites. The information may consist of both Personally Identifiable Information (“PII”) and Non-Personally Identifiable Information (“Non-PII”), and is collected in order to conduct business with current and prospective business clients. PII is information about a specific individual (i.e. name, contact information, or billing information) that is used to identify that individual. We do not sell or rent data collected via our Websites to other parties, but we may provide it to third parties as necessary to conduct our business operations and to our customers for the performance of our Services, or we may disclose such data as otherwise described in this policy. Altrooz uses these data to provide requested information to prospective clients, to establish self-service advertiser and publisher accounts, and otherwise as necessary to conduct our business. If you would like to review or request changes to PII that you have submitted through our Websites, or would like to request that we not share your PII with third parties, please contact us using the information below. 

Data Collected On Our Platform and from Partners. Altrooz collects Non-PII from across our Platform. This data, which may include anonymous identifiers associated with your mobile device and the precise location of your device (i.e. GPS or Wi-Fi data if you enable these services), does not identify you personally, and may come from such sources like your mobile web browser, or the apps that you use. We use a variety of technologies to collect this data, including “cookies,” which are small text files that can be stored on your browser. We may also collect and/or use information collected by our partners and shared with us, and data from third party business partners. We use this Non-PII (including device identifiers) along with our technology to perform a variety of tasks, such as improving the relevance of the ads, identifying possible relationships among different browsers and devices, limiting the number of times a specific advertisement is presented to the same mobile device (frequency capping), providing an advertisement to only certain types of mobile devices, or providing a report to a client on the number of its advertisements that were clicked. We may share this Non-PII with clients, vendors, and other companies with whom we conduct business, and as otherwise described in this policy. We may also use some of this data to provide interest-based advertising, as discussed more fully below. 

Other Information Sharing. Altrooz’s affiliated entities covered by this policy may share data with each other or with other affiliated entities. We may also share any aggregate or de-identified information with our partners. We may disclose information, including PII, when in our sole judgment we are required to do so by law, regulation, or when such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process. Additionally, there may be times where we will need to disclose information to protect our system or our rights or to ensure your safety or the safety of others. We may also transfer all or some of the data discussed in this policy, in connection with a corporate merger, acquisition, partial or total sale of assets, bankruptcy, or any other corporate change. 

##### Interest-Based Advertising and Opt Out

Altrooz works with its clients to provide ads that are likely to be more interesting and more relevant to mobile device users. One way we do this is by using our technology, along with Non-PII related to your mobile device that is gathered across different sources. Examples of this data, which does not identify you personally (Non-PII), may include things like mobile websites you have visited or mobile apps that you use, preferences that you may have provided to your app provider or to Altrooz (as in a survey), information collected by our partners and other third parties and shared with us, device identifiers, or location information (i.e. GPS or Wi-Fi data if you have enabled those services). We may link an identifier to additional data from other partners to provide us with some information about users’ likely interests (for example, that a user seems to be interested in purchasing a new car). When we have such information, the ads that we display to that user can be more relevant to his or her interests. 

Altrooz adheres to the Digital Advertising Alliance’s Self-Regulatory Principles. For more information about these Principles and the choices provided to you, you can visit www.aboutads.info. If you would like to opt out of the use of data for in-app advertisements, please download and use the appropriate Truste Ad Privacy Manager applications below based on your device’s operating system: 

##### Links to Third-Party Websites and Third-Party Content Websites

Our Websites may contain links to other websites, such as sites providing news coverage of the company, to partner sites for case studies, and to industry association sites of which Altrooz is a member. Altrooz is not responsible for the privacy notices or practices of these third-party websites. Ads. We may also provide ads that link to third-party sites, third-party apps, or other third-party content (“Third-Party Content”). This Privacy Policy does not extend to Third-Party Content, or any services offered on Third-Party Content. 

##### Data Collection On Behalf Of Third Parties

We may, on behalf of our clients and partners, collect information from end users. This may occur, for example, if someone submits information in response to an ad that we provide on behalf of an advertising client. Such information may consist of PII, non-PII, or both. In such situations, we collect the information and provide it to our client, and it will be subject to that client’s privacy practices. 

Children´s Privacy If you believe your child has provided Altrooz with personal information, such as by registering at one of Altrooz´s websites, and you would like to have the data removed, please contact us using the contact information below. 

Security Altrooz takes steps to protect the security of information that we collect. To that end, we have designed and deployed hardware, software, and networking solutions in an effort to reasonably secure and protect access to our systems and data. 

United States-European Union Safe Harbor and United States-Swiss Safe Harbor Altrooz is based in the United States, and, regardless of where you use our services or otherwise provide information to us, the information may be transferred to and maintained on servers located in the U.S. Please note that any information we obtain about you will be stored in accordance with U.S. privacy laws, regulations, and standards, which may not be equivalent to the laws in your country of residence. By using our Services or by providing us with your information, you consent to this collection, transfer, storage, and processing of information to and in the United States. 

For users of Altrooz provided in the EU, please be aware that your data may be transferred to Altrooz group entities and third parties located in countries that are not considered by the European Commission or other governmental agencies to offer adequate protection of your personal data. For these cases, Altrooz has put into place safeguards to ensure adequate protection of your data, such as (and to the extent applicable) European Commission-approved standard contractual clauses, your consent or other safeguards. 

##### Changes to Privacy Policy

Altrooz is committed to continually examining and reviewing its privacy practices, and may make changes to its Privacy Policy. In the event that any changes that we believe are material are made to the company´s privacy practices, we will post a revised Privacy Policy on this website. 

##### Questions and Concerns

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy practices, you may contact us: 

Altrooz, Inc.  
85 Liberty Ship Way, Suite 208  
Sausalito, CA 94965  
(415) 215-1760
